Indiana University Department of Radio and Television Chair's records, 1939-1963 C104
Indiana University Archives
Indiana University Department of Radio and Television Chair's records
1939-1963
1945-1952
Indiana University Archives
Indiana University. Department of Radio and Television
C104
14.8 cubic feet 16 boxes
In 1938, Indiana University began to engage in radio activities. A room was set aside for use as a studio and control room, and a radio director and program director were hired. For years, radio classes were taught through several already established departments such as Speech and Journalism. At the Board of Trustees September 20, 1945 meeting, they approved the establishment of a Dept. of Radio as an "unattached" department under the Dean of Faculties. In 1953 it became the Department of Radio and Television within the College of Arts and Sciences and in 1974 the Department of Telecommunications. This collection contains the department chair's records from 1939-1963 and is comprised of correspondence, budgetary information, annual reports, information on various radio and television stations, and subject files. Records span the tenures of chairs Harry Skornia (1942-1953) and Elmer Sulzer (1954-1964).
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Advance notice required for access.
Administrative History
In 1938, Indiana University began to engage in radio activities. A room was set aside for use as a studio and control room and a radio director and program director were hired. Courses such as "Radio Broadcasting" and "Radio Writing" were offered through the Department of Speech and "Radio News" in the Department of Journalism. In addition, two graduate courses were initiated: "Radio in Education" in the School in Education and "Radio Seminar" in the Department of Speech.
At the Board of Trustees September 20, 1945 meeting, they approved the establishment of a Department of Radio as an "unattached department" under the Dean of Faculties. Beginning the fall of 1950, IU offered a B.S. in Radio and listed the courses under the College of Arts and Sciences, but it wasn't until 1953 that Radio officially began a part COAS, when the Trustees approved the establishment of the Department of Radio and Television. In 1974, the Trustees approved a name change to the Department of Telecommunications in order to better reflect the expanded scope of their academic program. This change went into effect on July 1.
Harry Skornia served as Director of Radio Programs (and chair of the department once it was established) from 1942-1953. Following him was Elmer Sulzer, who chaired the department for the decade from 1954-1964. Sulzer was succeeded by Donley Feddersen, who served as department chair from 1966-1970.
Today the Department of Telecommunications is home to over forty faculty members. It offers courses in marketing strategies, multimedia design, radio and television production, processes and effects, and industry and management.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into four series: Correspondence; Administrative files; Radio and television shows; and Radio and television stations.
Scope and Content Note
This collection is organized into four series: Correspondence; Administrative files; Radio shows; and Radio and television stations. The Administrative files series is further organized into two sub-series: Annual reports and Subject files. The entire collection spans the years 1939-1963 and is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
The Correspondence series was created from files originally labeled "Miscellaneous," and is comprised of correspondence between the chair and colleagues within the University as well as outside contacts. Prominent correspondents include John Ashton, Herman Briscoe, William O. Aldridge, W.G. Biddle, Governor George N. Craig, Norman Ramsey, Dean Frank T. Gucker, and Herman B Wells, and officials from various state universities and several national organizations. The subject matter covered by the correspondence includes award nominations, information on former students, letters pertaining to radio programs at Universities outside of IU, fan mail and mailed questionnaires and surveys. The materials in this series span the period from 1942-1961.
Administrative files, 1937-1962, is the second series in the collection. This series is further organized into two sub-series: Annual reports and Subject files. The Annual reports sub-series includes departmental reports from 1937-1962. The second sub-series, Subject files, 1943-1961, contains records pertaining to various national associations, such as such as the AFM (American Film Market), the FCC (Federal Communications Commission),and the NAB (National Association of Broadcasters). The records in this sub-series deal mostly with radio and telecommunications, Indiana University policies and procedures, the radio-TV departments of other Universities, faculty matters, awards, and educational courses and programs.
The next series in the collection is Radio and Television shows, 1951-1961. It contains scripts of shows put on the air by Indiana University as well as memos and schedules relating to these shows including episodes of "University Spotlight," "Sunday news & sports," and "Once Upon a Time." The folders in this series are arranged alphabetically, and the folders containing records pertaining to television stations are marked as such.
The fourth series in the collection, Radio and television stations, contains information about radio and television stations from all over the United States, but mostly in the Midwest. Some of the folders contain transcripts of particular shows, while others contain show lists and show times listed according to time zone. Many of the school stations were contracted to air Indiana University's program, "School of the Sky". The records in this series span the period from 1943-1952.
Separated Material
Detailed budget files removed and discarded.
Twelve photographs depicting German radio sites transferred to the Archives Photographs collection.
Files entitled Space Plans and Space Requests transferred to the Archives Architectural Records. Please consult staff for details.
One cubic foot of records related to Herman B Wells post-WWII work in Germany removed, to be processed into Collection C75.
Acquisition Information
Accession 0174, 5139-5146
Radio broadcasting --Study and teaching (Higher) --Indiana --Bloomington.; Television broadcasting --Study and teaching (Higher) --Indiana --Bloomington.; Sulzer, Elmer Griffith -- Archives; Indiana University. Department of Radio and Television -- Archives; Indiana University. Department of Radio and Television -- Records and correspondence; Indiana University. Department of Radio and Television -- History -- Sources; Indiana University. Department of Radio -- Archives; Indiana University. Department of Radio -- Records and correspondence; Indiana University. Department of Radio -- History -- Sources; Skornia, Harry J. (Harry Jay), 1910-1991 -- Archives; Skornia, Harry J. (Harry Jay), 1910-1991 -- Correspondence; Sulzer, Elmer Griffith -- Correspondence
- Correspondence, 1942-1961 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, general (Box 1)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 1)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 1)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - "A", 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - Aldridge, William O., 1948-1949 (Box 1)
  - Alisky, Marvin, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Alleman, B.S., 1951 (Box 1)
  - Allen, Franklin S., 1949 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Office, 1953 (Box 1)
  - American Council on Education, 1950 (Box 1)
  - American Library Association, 1950-1951 (Box 1)
  - American Society of Composers, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Amin, Ghali, 1950-1951 (Box 1)
  - Ashland Oil and Refining Company, 1953 (Box 1)
  - Ashton, Dean J.W., Graduate School (Box 1)
    - 1951-1954 (Box 1)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 1)
    - 1957-1959 (Box 1)
  - Associated Program Service, 1946-1953 (Box 1)
  - Ashland Oil and Refining Company, 1955 (Box 1)
  - Athletic Broadcasts, 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - Atomic Energy, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Audio & Video Products Corp., 1949 (Box 1)
  - Audio Visual Center, 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - Awards (miscellaneous, Fulbright, etc), 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - Awards and Scholarships, 1956 (Box 1)
  - "B", 1959-1960 (Box 1)
  - B.S. Degree Requests for Information, 1947-1950 (Box 1)
  - Bain, Dean, 1947-1954 (Box 1)
  - Barnhouse, C.L., 1944 (Box 1)
  - Barnouw, Erik, 1947-1950 (Box 1)
  - Barret, Edward, 1949-1950 (Box 1)
  - Barriger, John W., 1952-1953 (Box 1)
  - Baruch, Ralph, 1950 (Box 1)
  - Becker, Sam, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Bing Crosby Enterprises, Inc., 1949 (Box 1)
  - Biddle, W.G., 1944-1945 (Box 1)
  - Billboard Magazine, 1948-1949 (Box 1)
  - Black, C.J., 1951-1954 (Box 1)
  - B.M.I. (Broadcast Music Inc.), 1953-1954 (Box 1)
  - Board of Health, Indiana State, undated (Box 1)
  - Boston University, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Braden, Samuel, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Brandes, Jean, 1949 (Box 1)
  - Bray, William G., 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - Bretz, Rudy, 1953 (Box 1)
  - Brewer, Fred, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Brickson, H.O., 1950 (Box 1)
  - Brill, Klaus, 1950 (Box 1)
  - Briscoe, Dean H.T., 1952-1954 (Box 1)
  - British Broadcasting Company, 1956-1959 (Box 1)
  - Broadcasting-Reader's Service, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Broadcasting Telecasting, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Broderick, Gertrude G., 1958 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Warren W., 1953 (Box 1)
  - Brookings Institute, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Buchanan, Mrs. Jewel Harris, 1953 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin, Mensuel, 1949 (Box 1)
  - Bureau of Teacher Recommendations, 1950 (Box 1)
  - Busch, William R., 1949-1950 (Box 1)
  - Bureau of Personnel Relations and Placement, Indiana University, 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - Business, School of, 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - "C", 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - California, University of, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Canadian Broadcasting Corp., 1949 (Box 1)
  - Capehart, Senator Homer, 1949 (Box 1)
  - Capitol Transcriptions, 1953-1954 (Box 1)
  - Causey, J.L., 1951 (Box 1)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1944 (Box 1)
  - Census Bureau, 1950 (Box 1)
  - Chen, L.K., 1950 (Box 1)
  - "Children's Record Guild", 1951 (Box 1)
  - Cisler, Steve, 1949-1952 (Box 1)
  - Case, Clare, 1947 (Box 1)
  - Coburn, Charles, 1953 (Box 1)
  - Collins Radio Company, 1949 (Box 1)
  - College Quiz Bowl, 1953-1954 (Box 1)
  - Collins, Dean, 1953-1960 (Box 1)
  - Colorado, University of, 1944-1949 (Box 1)
  - Columbia Broadcasting, 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - Condon, Richard J., 1948-1950 (Box 1)
  - Congratulatory Letters (Box 1)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 1)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 1)
  - Copyright and clearance (Box 1)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 1)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 1)
    - Advisory committee, 1949-1950 (Box 1)
    - 1960 (Box 1)
  - Courier-Times, 1952 (Box 1)
  - Crackpot mail, 1942-1946 (Box 1)
  - Craig, George N. (governor), 1954 (Box 1)
  - Cramer, Edward M., 1958 (Box 1)
  - Crask, Lamar, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Creative Broadcasting, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Crosley Broadcasting Co., 1957 (Box 1)
  - "D", 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - Dawson, Donald D., 1951 (Box 1)
  - Day, M. McCabe, 1950 (Box 1)
  - "Dedications", 1950 (Box 1)
  - Delta Upsilon Fraternity, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Denny, Judith, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - De Pauw University (Box 1)
    - 1957 (Box 1)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 1)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 1)
  - Diagnostic Tests, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Displays, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Drapery Inquiries, 1950 (Box 1)
  - Dunagin, Ruth, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Dunlap, Chester, 1950 (Box 1)
  - Dutton, Jane, 1953 (Box 1)
  - "E", 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - Educational Television and Radio Center (Box 1)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 1)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - Electrical Tower Service, 1950 (Box 1)
  - Ellis Trucking Co., Inc., 1955 (Box 1)
  - Ellson, D.G., 1958 (Box 1)
  - Engineers, Radio (Applicants as), 1949-1950 (Box 1)
  - Evaluation, 1950-1951 (Box 1)
  - Everyday Nutrition, TV series, 1956 (Box 1)
  - "F", 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - Faculties, Dean of, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Fan Mail, 1959-1961 (Box 1)
  - F.C.C. (Federal Communications Commission), 1950-1958 (Box 2)
  - Feirabend, George C., 1957-1959 (Box 2)
  - Florida East Coast Railroad, 1959 (Box 2)
  - FM promotion, 1957-1960 (Box 2)
  - Ford Foundation, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Fortson, Ben W., 1959 (Box 2)
  - Fox, Kit (Mrs. James Shouse), 1956 (Box 2)
  - French Broadcasting System, 1949-1953 (Box 2)
  - French Lick music festival, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Former students, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - "From Freedom's Forge", 1951-1952 (Box 2)
  - Funk and Wagnalls Publishing Co., 1958 (Box 2)
  - "G", 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Galarno, William, 1950-1951 (Box 2)
  - Gates, Pat, 1948 (Box 2)
  - Gates radio company, 1952 (Box 2)
  - "Gateway", 1951 (Box 2)
  - Gebhard, Jack, 1950-1951 (Box 2)
  - "General Electric", 1947-1951 (Box 2)
  - Gerber, Fred L., 1947 (Box 2)
  - Germans, Letters from and to, 1948-1949 (Box 2)
  - Godley, Paul Company, 1948 (Box 2)
  - Government, Department of, 1953 (Box 2)
  - Governor's Conference, 1956 (Box 2)
  - Graduate School Bulletin (requests pending), 1959 (Box 2)
  - Grants, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Grewe, H.G., 1959 (Box 2)
  - Gary Research & Development Co., Inc., 1950 (Box 2)
  - Gucker, Frank T., Dean, 1951-1953 (Box 2)
  - Guest Speakers (Box 2)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 2)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - "H", 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Hall, Ford P., Dean, 1947-1948 (Box 2)
  - Halterman, Jean C., 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Hallicrafters, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Hennock, commissioner, 1949 (Box 2)
  - Herschell, Wm., 1943 (Box 2)
  - H.I.C.O.G. (Office of the United States High Commissioner for Germany), 1948-1950 (Box 2)
  - Hill, Harold E., 1950-1951 (Box 2)
  - Hodapp, William, 1949-1956 (Box 2)
  - Hoosier workshop, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Hotels, 1950-1951 (Box 2)
  - "I", 1958-1960 (Box 2)
  - Indiana Mental Hygiene Society, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Indiana State Library, 1943-1947 (Box 2)
  - Indianapolis Public Library, 1944 (Box 2)
  - Insurance, 1950-1951 (Box 2)
  - Interdepartmental correspondence, 1949-1951 (Box 2)
  - Interference correspondence answers from manufacturers, 1950 (Box 2)
  - Interlochen, 1950 (Box 2)
  - I.B.A. (Indiana Broadcaster's Association), Carl W. Vandagrift, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Indiana Broadcaster's Association (Box 2)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 2)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 2)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 2)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 2)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 2)
      General
      (FM Survey, Sulzer)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 2)
      (FM survey, Sulzer)
  - Indiana conference of higher education (Box 2)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 2)
    - 1957 (Box 2)
  - Indiana Council for Children and Youth (Box 2)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 2)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 2)
      (Mildred French)
  - Indiana League for Nursing, 1957-1958 (Box 2)
  - Indiana League for Nursing, 1957-1958 (Box 2)
  - Indianapolis Transit System, Inc., 1954 (Box 2)
  - Indiana Tuberculosis Association, Inc., 1956 (Box 2)
  - Introduction to Typewriting, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Irregularities, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - I.U. Extension Centers, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - I.U. Showboat, 1960 (Box 2)
  - I.U. Visitors, 1950 (Box 2)
  - "J", 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Jacobs, Louise M., 1959 (Box 2)
  - Job applications- IURTS (Non-academic), 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Job Inquiries- students, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Job openings- non-academic, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Joint Council on Educational Television, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Journalism, Department of, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Journal of Broadcasting (Box 2)
    - 1957 (Box 2)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 2)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - "K", 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Kay's correspondence, 1960 (Box 2)
  - K.C.V.N., 1950-1953 (Box 2)
  - Kearney, Owen, 1952-1953 (Box 2)
  - Kentucky Broadcasters Association, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Kentucky, University of (Box 2)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 2)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 2)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - K.F.J.M. (North Dakota), 1948-1949 (Box 2)
  - K.F.K.U., 1950-1951 (Box 2)
  - Kine correspondence, other than the "Let's See" series, 1958-1960 (Box 2)
  - Kine network correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 2)
  - Kinescope network (Box 2)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 2)
    - Affiliates meeting, 1939-1963 (Box 2)
  - Kinescope Traffic (J. Denny) (Box 2)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 2)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 2)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - K.O.A.C. (School of the Air), 1947-1951 (Box 2)
  - K.O.K.H., 1953 (Box 2)
  - K.T.J.O.-FM, 1951 (Box 2)
  - "L", 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Ladd, Bill (courier-journal), 1956-1957 (Box 2)
  - Lake Central Airlines, 1954-1955 (Box 2)
  - Lambert, C. Wesley, 1956-1957 (Box 2)
  - Library of Congress Photoduplication Service, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Loans (Box 2)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 2)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 2)
  - Long, Chet, 1950 (Box 2)
  - Louisville Radio School (Box 2)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 2)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - "M", 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - M.A. degree in radio, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Macmillan Co.- "The Bears of Blue River", 1951 (Box 2)
  - Maier, John V., 1950 (Box 2)
  - Marks, Edward B., Music Corp., 1944 (Box 3)
  - Matthew Bender and Company, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Memorandums, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Memorandums to staff (Box 3)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 3)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Men's faculty club, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Metropolitan Opera broadcasts, 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Miami, University of, 1949 (Box 3)
  - Michael, Ada L., 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Michigan, University of, 1957-1958 (Box 3)
  - Ministerial Association, 1947-1948 (Box 3)
  - Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous campus correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 3)
  - Mr. Seltz, 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Munn, Mark, 1952-1954 (Box 3)
  - Music Corporation of America, 1951 (Box 3)
  - "Music in the Life of Man" (two folders), 1958-1960 (Box 3)
  - Music performance trust fund, 1949 (Box 3)
  - Music, school of, 1957-1958 (Box 3)
  - Muzak Corporation, 1951 (Box 3)
  - "N", 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - N.A.E.B. (National Association of Educational Broadcasters), 1957-1959 (Box 3)
  - Nakano, Taeko, 1951 (Box 3)
  - National Safety Council, 1951-1965 (Box 3)
  - Netherlands Information Bureau, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Norwegian Information Service, 1951 (Box 3)
  - News Bureau, 1957-1958 (Box 3)
  - News Directors Association, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Newsletter, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Odor, Joan, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Ohio State University (Box 3)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 3)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 3)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 3)
    - (Miscellaneous), 1959 (Box 3)
  - Ohio State University (Harrison B. Summers), 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Operatic Telecasts, 1956-1957 (Box 3)
  - Orchids, 1943-1951 (Box 3)
  - "Overseas" short wave programs, 1942-1943 (Box 3)
  - "P", 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Paulu, (Dr.) Burton, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Pinckney, Lawrence R., 1957 (Box 3)
  - "Prentice Hall", 1950-1951 (Box 3)
  - "Problems in Everyday Speech", 1947-1950 (Box 3)
  - Program in Reserve, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Programming, 1957-1958 (Box 3)
  - Public health series, 1951 (Box 3)
  - Publications office, 1953-1954 (Box 3)
  - Publication requests, 1957-1958 (Box 3)
  - Publicity (Box 3)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 3)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 3)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Public Relations committee, 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Questionnaires (Surveys) (Box 3)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 3)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 3)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - "R", 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Radio courses, information on, 1951 (Box 3)
  - Radio guild, 1951 (Box 3)
  - Radio-Television committee, 1956-1957 (Box 3)
  - Ramsey, Norman, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Recompense for faculty doing extended TV credit courses, 1957-1958 (Box 3)
  - Record clearance, 1943-50 (Box 3)
  - Record services, 1956-1957 (Box 3)
  - Registrar's Office, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Releases, literary, 1942-1946 (Box 3)
  - Releases, musical, 1943-1946 (Box 3)
  - Religion, 1949-1951 (Box 3)
  - Requests (miscellaneous), 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Research in Indiana's industries, 1956-1957 (Box 3)
  - Restricted materials, 1949 (Box 3)
  - Richter, Wilbur J., 1958 (Box 3)
  - Rippetoe, Farrell, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Ritchie, H. Roscoe Jr., 1949 (Box 3)
  - Robert, E. Lee, 1952-1953 (Box 3)
  - Rodeman, Norbert R, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Rotary club (district meeting), 1953 (Box 3)
  - R.P.M. magazine, 1949 (Box 3)
  - "S" (Box 3)
    - 1955-1957 (Box 3)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Safety Division, 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Salisbury, Leah, 1949-1950 (Box 3)
  - Salzburg Festival program, 1949-1950 (Box 3)
  - Sarkes Tarzian Inc., 1957-1959 (Box 3)
  - S.B.C., 1950 (Box 3)
  - Schmitt, Hall and McCreary Co., 1958 (Box 3)
  - School of Music, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Schricker, Henry- Fletcher Trust Co., Indianapolis, IN, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Script contests, 1947-1948; undated (Box 3)
  - Seagram & Sons, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Setlz, Herbert (Box 3)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 3)
    - 1959 (Box 3)
  - Service enterprises, 1954 (Box 3)
  - S.E.S.A.C. (Society of European Stage Authors & Composers) (Box 3)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 3)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 3)
  - Shapiro, Bernstein & Co. Inc, New York, NY, 1944 (Box 3)
  - Shattinger Piano & Music Co., 1944 (Box 3)
  - Shaw, Clifford, 1949-1950 (Box 3)
  - Shaw, Julie, 1950-1951 (Box 3)
  - "Singing Hoosiers", 1956-1957 (Box 3)
  - Smith, Dave, 1949-1951 (Box 3)
  - Special services to organizations, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Staff, 1947-1949 (Box 3)
  - Standard, 1952-1954 (Box 3)
  - Standard Radio Transcription Service, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Stanford Press, 1958 (Box 3)
  - State of Indiana- Educational Television committee, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Stromberg, Carlson, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Stout, Clarence, 1944-1950 (Box 3)
  - Survey- requests and reactions, 1949 (Box 3)
  - "T", 1959 (Box 3)
  - Television (I.U.R.T.S. - Indiana University Radio & Television Station), 1956-1957 (Box 3)
  - Television Age-Readers Service, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Tele-prompter, 1957 (Box 3)
  - TV rehearsal camera, 1950 (Box 3)
  - TV- Transportation, 1954-1956 (Box 3)
  - Thompson, Robert, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Torch club, 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Traffic manager, 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Travel requests, 1958 (Box 3)
  - UAW-CIO workshop, 1949 (Box 4)
  - United Nations, 1947-1951 (Box 4)
  - United Nations Radio, 1951 (Box 4)
  - United press machine, 1950-1951 (Box 4)
  - University Broadcasting Committee, 1957 (Box 4)
  - U.S. Army, 1950 (Box 4)
  - U.S. Government Printing Office, 1958-1959 (Box 4)
  - U.S. Navy, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Van Horn, Glen, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Variety, 1958 (Box 4)
  - "Visiting Indiana's Industries", 1952-1953; (two folders) (Box 4)
  - Visiting experts, 1948-1949 (Box 4)
  - Visiting foreigners radio, 1949 (Box 4)
  - "W", 1958-1959 (Box 4)
  - Waggoner, G.R. Assistant Dean- College of Arts and Sciences, 1949-1954 (Box 4)
  - Wagenfuhr, Dr. Kurt, 1949-1951 (Box 4)
  - Weber, Walter, 1954 (Box 4)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1957 (Box 4)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Williams, Martin, 1948 (Box 4)
  - William, John C.-WITZ, 1955 (Box 4)
  - Wilson, Walt, 1953-1954 (Box 4)
  - World Radio Systems, 1948 (Box 4)
  - "Y", 1958-1959 (Box 4)
  - Yarrington, Bancroft, 1954 (Box 4)
  - "Z", 1958-1959 (Box 4)
- Administrative files, 1937-1962
  - Annual Reports, 1937-1962
    - Departmental reports (Box 4)
      - Radio broadcasting five year report, 1937-1943 (Box 4)
      - Radio broadcasting, 1942-1944 (Box 4)
      - 1937-1938 (Box 4)
      - 1938-1939 (Box 4)
      - 1939-1940 (Box 4)
      - 1942-1944 (Box 4)
      - 1944-1945 (Box 4)
      - 1946-1947 (Box 4)
      - 1947-1948 (Box 4)
      - 1948-1949, (three folders) (Box 4)
      - 1949-1950, (two folders) (Box 4)
      - 1950-1951 (Box 4)
      - 1954-1955 (Box 4)
      - 1955-1956 (Box 4)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 4)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 4)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 4)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 4)
      - 1960-1961 (Box 4)
      - 1961-1962 (Box 4)
    - Annual report materials, 1949-1951 (Box 4)
    - Faculty annual reports (Box 4)
      - H. J. Skornia, 1942-1951 (Box 4)
      - Various (Box 4)
        - 1951-1952 (Box 4)
        - 1952-1953 (Box 4)
        - 1953-1954 (Box 4)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 4)
  - Subject files, 1939-1963
    - AAUP (American Association of University Professors), 1951-1953 (Box 4)
    - ACPRA (American College Public Relations Association) (Box 4)